um
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
is that how karma works
we're good to go
let's go
okay
our first speaker in the afternoon
session motion daniel how many people
here saw his workshop thursday
so some of you about half of you
okay it was extraordinary
and today he's going to be presenting
more on the philosophy
he is a naturopathic doctor he graduated
in 2000 uh at the canada college of
natural medicine
and he is specializing in homeopathy
which is part of what gave him the
insights that make this technology
possible
he's also an author he has a book on the
kabbalah and natural medicine
and he's
written one book that's called the last
four books of moses
he's very interested in chemical and
healing aspects
because the world
needs this healing just as much as any
human body does so here is moshe daniel
hi
thanks man thanks a lot
appreciate it
so i did a talk a few days ago which was
kind of like part two of this this
lecture
and so what i'm going to be sharing
today is how
the technologies that are emerging in
particular the mojo cell
is actually a reflection of where our
consciousness is at right now and where
we're evolving as a human race
so this is really exciting stuff really
exciting and very powerful and as we
evolve
to a race that supports each other that
helps each other that has a an idea of
abundance that as i give so i receive
then our technologies are also going to
be reflecting that
and as a result of it we won't be using
this explosive
poisonous
toxic
substance to empower our our systems
so
thank you so much for coming
also today what i will be sharing is an
advanced form of the mojo cell
which i'm calling the sphinx sphere
and it really it came to me that i
needed to share this after seeing some
of the lectures in particular dr len
horowitz's talk which i saw a couple of
days ago yesterday actually
time is uh strange these these moments
so uh
mike forgot to introduce albie
this is alby right here
and he's he's been a
a part of this since the beginning
so
the mojo technology began with joe
now the history is a little bit
fuzzy some say that joe this this
gentleman
in
australia
wanted to run his car on steam so use
high voltage leads with stainless steel
plates
and he was running his car on steam and
then he noticed that even when he dis
dislodge or unattached the leads that
the car kept running
another story goes that
peter
and joe
peter stevens and joe booker went to
this presentation by a man named graham
co
and graham was presenting this
technology that his grandfather had
taught him
that they used in the tanks in the
german tanks in the second world war
and that puts us in the in the nazi
realm and the nazis had victor
schauberger and got a lot of technology
from schalberger so what the joe cell
may actually be
is a form of technology that's come from
victor schauberger
and possibly what they were using also
to power their u-boats which enabled
them to run indefinitely underwater and
they only needed to surface to
feed the men
this is a picture of the the the joe
cell
and this was my uh some of my joe cell
results i got really good results stage
three water foam galore
so um i learned a lot from the joe cell
technology but as soon as i i heard
about the joe cell technology
i knew i had to go to a spherical form
that i understood a little bit about
what how it was working i don't think
anybody understands full yet
and if they do
i wonder what they're really
understanding
part of it is a mystery so far i'm not
saying that it won't be understood fully
but so far we don't know 100
but i have some theories that i will
share with you
so this was the first set of steel it
had no holes it had no spacers it was
kind of rusty leads in the water
very makeshift but getting good results
as soon as i went to the spherical form
that the water was charging faster the
energy field was incredible
and what i felt with the joe cell was
this amazing energy field
basically i i've been uh sensitive with
oregon technologies i've been working
with oregon technologies since i'm very
a lot younger
i built oregon accumulator accumulators
been working with orgonite so it was
sensitive to the energy field of the joe
cell when i went to the mojo cell it was
off the charts no comparison a lot more
strong a lot more uh vigorous a lot more
obvious
alex schiffer who is the author of the
experimental guide to the experimenter's
guide to the joe cell uh described said
this the spherical cells are far
superior to the concentric cylindrical
type cells his contention with the the
mojo cell the spherical cell was that
how do you get the energy out of the
center
how do you extract the energy from the
center that was his contention and i
i'll explain that that that's really a a
sort of a linear way of thinking that
the energy has a field effect that it's
affecting a radius far beyond its
physical dimensions and it really is
radiating uh without worrying about
extracting it from the center but there
are ways of extracting as well
so here is some of the the old design
where you see the aluminum tape
really shabby job
and then you have the the buna n spacers
when i switched to ebonite as a spacer
the results improved tremendously buna-n
was shorting out the cell and some of
the better substances to use as spacers
are teflon
and ebonite i would say are the top two
and then polycarbonate is good nylon is
good very good
and this is this was the improved design
having a lip which i call the female
cell which slots into the male cell
enabling for a perfect centering of the
see the spheres within the spheres
so if we go back you see the spheres
within the spheres but with the spacers
sometimes it was on sometimes it was a
little off so with the with these
um with the lip it became really like
like beautiful perfection
and you see here just how it assembles
from the inside to the outside with the
the nylon spacers
tightening
the cell altogether whoops
and and as you see it's beautiful and
that if you look at the top this is what
i call the smoke stack effect this is a
water charging kit and when the water
charging kit gets going see when you
first start charging the water with the
cell the steel is basically dormant it
doesn't know what it what it is it
doesn't know if it's a spoon a knife it
doesn't know if it's a mojo cell
when you start to charge it it starts to
gain this this this awareness
which is a awareness of what its role is
and it starts to hold a charge longer
and longer and after a few days you
start to get a smoke stacking effect of
of the gas which is
the purpose of the mojo cell it's not a
gas producer there are a lot more
efficient forms to produce hydrogen or
hhho gas the mo it's just a sign that
the water is charged when you see the
smoke stack like a thick billowing cloud
of smoke because at the beginning you'll
get sporadic bubbles and then it'll
start to get thicker and then it will
start to accumulate on the surface
and so my dear attractive assistant john
well
[Music]
the lights went out after i turn on the
cell
by mistake
so you see the bubbles accumulating on
the surface like a
cafe latte sort of consistency
wow
sir
yep
we can drink that
[Music]
uh
that
that was me breathing on it
i don't know if can you feel that from
the video do you feel the energy
radiating from the video i know it
doesn't make logical sense
with energy
yeah the whole container is is filled
with water and it's a and it's above the
water so if i could get uh back to
oh okay yeah yeah good
okay so you saw the water you heard the
sizzle when i breathed on it the bubbles
went
that's a sign of highly charged water
and in fact if you have water with the
joe cell process or the mojo process and
you're charging it and it's covered and
then you open it and the bubbles start
to pop at that moment that's a sign of
of what's called stage three water so
some of the results that we've had with
our car installations have been varied
we've had we've had immediate results
where we noticed a change in the
performance of the vehicle
and this is uh just a picture of the
honda installation
where i went into the air intake
and then we have a picture of the land
rover 2001
where we drove from florida to texas and
we had a boost in performance and at one
point we we started to see uh
about a boost from 12.1 miles per gallon
to 17.5 which was really good and that's
without any oxygen sensor tweaks or any
without changing the ecu
and this is an installation in alexis
just to show you some of the examples
one of the one of the common themes is
that we have our cell installed where we
can find a space
and we have a tube carrying the energy
into the vacuum intake which is the the
best place to install
now some of the results
all of the results showed a boost in
performance
so we know the cell is affecting the
engine
performance honda yes land rover yes
lexus yes and this gmc gentleman said
car seems to run better improvement in
the quality of the air conditioner runs
cooler
why not
the honda accord that i drove was like
the the pedal was very much more
sensitive and i felt like i was gliding
like almost like a hovercraft the tires
were on the ground though but soon soon
we shall have that that will change as
well
um in the lexus in the land rover as i
said yes we had a performance the
handling better handling yes increased
speed the car is quieter and has a
softer feel
and then fuel mileage improvement i
didn't get any in the honda accord
um and none that i could measure
the it's a small car four-cylinder
engine i didn't see a fuel mileage
improvement i needed to go into the ecu
i need to hack the ecu for that that's
coming that will be coming
the um the land rover yes we we got the
boost the lexus got a boost from 16 to
27 overall and this big monster yukon
denali went from 12.9 to 17.9 miles per
gallon overall and on the highway it
went from 14.9 to 22.
the installation here was air intake
land rover is actually the vacuum intake
i made a mistake here and we got vacuum
and vacuum vacuum is the way to go
so the present stumbling blocks in this
technology as i i just discussed is
the car company i didn't say this but
the car company secrecy
and the status quo of straight jacketing
fuel mileage one thing that's happening
with the joe cell world is people are
trying to get into their car computers
to improve their technology and also
hydrogen world and we're seeing this the
very strong control that the car
computer has on fuel mileage
uh back in the day with carburetors a
person can learn a little bit about cars
open up the hood and tweak it and
improve their fuel mileage
but the the car companies are are very
secretly holding the information the
knowledge of how to improve their fuel
mileage um there's a man that i respect
highly on the the joe cell group
his name is bernie and he says that if
you got an engineer who was allowed free
reign on the ecu just by tweaking it to
enhance it rather than have the status
quo of crappy fuel mileage you could
probably improve it uh
60 70 miles per gallon just with the
just with the car computer i i believe
he's right because we've gone backwards
with our technology uh with the cars and
besides it's a it's it's a we're using a
combustion engine which is so old so
many improved engines have emerged on
the market that we don't have access to
another uh straight jacket problem or
stumbling block the ecu lockdown as i
said
which one of the tech one of the
technologies that we're looking at is
mega squirting and tweaking it with
laptop
o2 and map sensor tweaking which i tried
and didn't have good results
i
don't like this as the solution there's
got to be a better solution which we're
looking into basically you tweak the
oxygen sensor and then you and then you
have to put the map sensor up to balance
it or your car doesn't run in the same
performance
so we're looking at at finding solutions
here and if anybody has solutions that
they trust in we're all ears we're all
ears here's one of the methods of
charging which i show on my website
mojoworking.com and uh under the
charging page so you take your you take
your wall
you plug into your wall you got a variac
60 to 80 bucks for a variac this is a 5
amp variac
you take you put it into your bridge
rectifier
this is not drawn to scale
put your ac here you get your dc out
positive into your capacitor goes to the
positive of the cell negative goes into
your negative capacitor into the
negative of the cell that's what i was
using with that highly charged water
video you just saw so it's great for the
water charging kit to purify the water
to enhance the water to get it to the
stage you want it to be
another system is pepe's circuit a 12
volt bizarrely effective method
i say it's bizarrely effective because
it makes no sense what's going on but
this guy is
i want to call him a genius but i i
don't i don't use that that term lightly
he's very advanced in his thinking and
he's from the parts of the the alps he's
in croatia very close to where
schallberger wilhelm reich and tesla all
came from so he's drinking good water
and he's and his brain has evolved
it's true though it's amazing like you
have good water your consciousness is
good
you have bad water you're living in a
city you're drinking water from a tap
and you're putting it through a brita
filter and you're drinking that all day
you're dumbing yourself down because the
water is dead
it's very it's true and right now we're
in the age of aquarius the age of the
aquarius is the water bearer it's the
age of water and we are blessed to be
understanding the secrets of water how
far water brings us and and that the
fact that we are made up mostly of water
okay so i won't get into this too much
but you could go to the charging uh
the charging page on mojo working you
just see that you have a bridge
rectifier 12 volt transformer you have a
weird coil here that's wrapped around a
pencil
uh a diode zener diode and a resistor
and when we charge it with this method
we could charge longer the charge builds
up and you really feel the effect like
you really feel beautiful beautiful
effect everybody can feel it
so how does this technology work
the secret lies in diamagnetism
diamagnetism is weak repulsion from a
magnetic field
it is a form of magnetism that is only
exhibited by a substance in the presence
of an externally applied magnetic field
from wikipedia so here we see a
diamagnetic substance being levitated
you see this it's levitating
over a magnet because when the magnet
applies its force it starts to repel
against the magnet and it will levitate
it's very thin and it feel the strong so
it has it can levitate and they also
show this with the frogs
where'd my water go aha
speaking of water
the diamagnetic substances are usually
non-magnetic
including water
and and substances like petroleum carbon
some plastics and and many of the metals
copper
uh
mercury gold and bismuth so if the water
in the center of the cell is exposed to
a magnetic field from the spheres
where does it create its repelling
magnetic field
in other words what we just saw up here
is that this is being repelled but it
creates a repelling magnetic field and
its force pushes it up against the the
magnets and it's able to levitate but if
we surround
surround the water in the center of the
inner sphere
where does the water create a magnetic
field
so if we look this is our inner sphere
and we apply in the the negative
electricity we get we get a magnetic
field that is created
because of the application of the
electricity very simple
and then we we put uh uh the five inch
over that there are two there are two
spheres in between that act as neutral
plates
which enhances this whole effect
we put the positive on the top
and we create a magnetic field of pot
what we could call positive electricity
on the outside and negative on the
inside
now this generates
the magic
this is where the technology of the mojo
cell works and also the joe cell but
here you'll understand why the mojo cell
the spherical form is superior
because if you have water in the inside
of your cell that is surrounded by a
magnetic field
where does it create the weak
repulsional field
into itself
it's surrounded
it has to go into its center
that we call implosion we call this
negative magnetism we call it going into
the vacuum and coming out on the other
side of reality
the the scientist male m-e-y-l proposes
that what is being created at this point
are neutrinos
the neutrinos created are created
because of the balance of the positive
and the negative so you have something
that sounds like an
something that's neutral
which is fantastic
and these go in these seek out a high
voltage source and are converted into
electrons they absorb energy from the
atmosphere and and also heat and they
release energy when they're converted
into the electrons
i think it could be some form of
antimatter that we're creating some sort
of negative electrons or positrons
hydronium ions
that
are perhaps not typical in that they
don't seek matter instantly and explode
but also somehow are seeking the high
voltage ignition spark to marry
themselves with their counterpart on the
other side of reality which is the side
of reality of our physical world where
we are now
and
that releases energy that runs the car
so like i said i'm just proposing some
ideas my feeling my gut feeling from my
experience from working is that it has
all to do with the magnetism surrounding
the diamagnetic substance
now what's amazing about this is that
we're creating something that doesn't
exist in nature which is a spherical
magnet
a magnet whose south pole is on the
inside whose north pole is on the
outside in a three-dimensional
multi-dimensional
every dimensional form
doesn't exist in nature all magnets are
linear
one in once in one pole and out the
other we have a three-dimensional
magnet whose zero-point field is created
in the center every magnet has a neutral
center where the south becomes the north
and that is where they hold hands and
they are neither south
nor north individually but are both and
neither it is the undefined nature of
the zero point field so we're creating
that right in the center
of this
by applying the the male
now we're going to get into a little
alchemy here
the female
and creating our male female energy from
the vacuum
from the undefined infinite nature of
creation
here is where our technologies are
marrying where we are coming from
where we've come from and where we are
going to
who are those
two adam and eve right
this is the account of the descendants
of adam on the day that god created
human
men
he made him in the likeness of god now
this is a gender biased
old testament translation
he created them male and female
he blessed them on the day and called
their name man on the day they were
created so really this should say
he she
created
them in the likeness of god what is the
likeness of god that the old testament
is saying that the kabbalistic model is
saying
male and female
is the nature of god to keep it very
simple a balance of male and female
and we see this is genesis 5 1 2 but
here's another quote just in case you
didn't get the first one the second one
will get your attention
so god created man in his image in the
image of god he created him male and
female he created them
here we go male and female genesis 5
and
genesis 1 27.
planet earth where's planet earth where
do we identify earth
what are these two planets
we got mars
and we got venus
planet earth exists between the two
planets and our stars in our solar
system which represent the planet of the
male
and the planet of the female
planet earth is meant to be a place of
balance
and yet
have we been in a place of balance for
the last many thousands of years
if we look at this tree this is the tree
of life
kabbalistic tree of life the roots of
the tree of life are in
the earth
which we call the mother the mother is
the female
the female is the source of the life
just like in the mojo cell the center of
the sphere
is where the life starts from because
that is where the undefined infinite
nature of creation emerges from from the
inner core
and then the male becomes the extension
the the the branches that reach up into
the sky
the male is as a balance important with
the female absolutely but in order to
understand the balanced positive nature
of reality that is the kabbalistic adam
cadmon the original adam who was one
with god as we truly are but have
forgotten
then the female must be the root the
foundation and mathematically
i'm a really i'm a simple guy my brain
doesn't go into complicated spaces
mathematically i put the female on the
bottom and the male on the top
but the female can be on the top and the
male can be on the bottom depends on
which application we're looking at here
mathematically i attribute
the open zero
the zeroness to being a feminine energy
female open my sense of self i am of
myself nothing
nothing the male is a singular
consciousness of i am something
so it's one
so comparing yin and yang zero and one
we got zero on as a foundation and one
at the top mathematically what does this
equal
infinity it's actually undefined and
that is what infinity is you cannot
define infinity as each of us evolves to
the source where we've come from the
balanced positive nature of reality as
we evolve and return
we return to the state of being
infinite and that is to be in a
consciousness which is undefined but is
something
which is two things that are opposites
married as one
it's it's fascinating men it's wonderful
so that equals like we said infinity now
what's happened in the last many
thousands of years as it said in the old
testament that when adam and eve ate
from the the tree of knowledge that god
turned to eve and said because you've
done this
greatly will your birthing pains be in
agony you'll bring forward children and
yet your craving will be for your
husband and he shall rule over you
and that is a prediction for the way
things would be
on this planet with the male dominating
the female and that is because
mars is nature when when the male and
female are one mars serves as a warrior
of love
absolutely essential for the balanced
nature of love
absolutely
but when there is separation which was
caused by the male by the the tree of
knowledge for good and bad mars can't
help himself
he's the he's the god of war
he's the god of competition singularity
needs to be number one that's why the
male has dominated the female for
thousands of years
in religion in science in education in
politics
whoops going backwards let's go this way
so when we look at that mathematically
what do we have
we have
the the male attempting to be the
foundation saying i am like god
i rule this place
we have the one
on the bottom of the equation
mathematically what does that equal
squat
nada
we've been living in in a a lie
where the male has attempted to dominate
the the foundation of creation
where the female truly is the source of
life where the water springs from the
infinite infinite life waters
the infinite life waters give rise and
then the male is essential otherwise the
female would stagnate in place and have
no ability to affect the the world or
affect its environment the mail
disseminates spreads uses protects
stores
this is true in chinese medicine it's
true in alchemy it's true in kabbalah
it's a universal simple truth
this is the tree of life reality
where the female is allowed to be the
source which in in a human being means
that we intuitively
do we do we got paul on the phone um
yeah well we just
can we stop can we pause the tape for a
moment please
okay
pause folks yeah
thanks we're back folks that that was
very moving
and i'd like to just address this point
in this day and age
what's that albie
oh he wants me to share
an excellent quote that he
came up with it and during his days
i hope i get it right
great spirits
have always encountered violent
opposition from mediocre minds
and that's been true through throughout
history and it's in the ether
you know if you
if you get outside of the way of the
church you get put up on the stake or
you get excommunicated if you come out
with a beautiful healing technology to
free the world you get persecuted
perhaps killed
and
people who want to die for god have it
backwards
no no one should want to die for god the
the life that we each of us has been
given
is the greatest gift that we have
and and and we should want to live till
the the end of days and beyond and
beyond because every moment is sacred so
our lives are precious
however we should not stop
being ourselves if
it may lead to
our demise
now that doesn't mean that we seek out
death that we that we are acting in a
fashion that is foolish i think we
should really be wise in this day and
age and and be aware but the more and
more people live their lives to the
fullest and bring forward this
technology it will not be able to be
suppressed anymore and people like paul
pantone
and wilhelm wright
and even john keeley who didn't die but
he was oppressed in his time we're
talking over 150 years ago 130 years ago
they
have not died in vain they have not
suffered in vain and their spirits are
here with us
like this is such a beautiful uh
conference
that we are able to share this freely
and and disseminate knowledge and go
really profoundly
into these technologies that are going
to be healing the world
you know if any one of these genius
minds uh in particular nikola tesla
wilhelm wright
john keeley if any one of them had had
their way and had been supported
our world would be free right now
because as topher has explained to me
every dollar
in the economy has 80 cents behind it
that goes to energy
so if you have free energy right away
you have instant abundance everybody is
freed
to be who they are and to to live as
they wish to live
which is to be in the tree of life
to be a balanced positive being both
male and female not warring between the
male and the female and vying for number
one and
one thing i do want to point out which
is very important
through time in history women have
identified with the female energy
they are built
readily resonant with the female their
error has been to suppress in themselves
the male energy
men
have identified readily with mars with
male and have been encouraged to be mar
martian like
male
their error has been to suppress the
female within them
each one of us is both male and female
that is what sets us free
that is the dance of love so that the
the woman is not the provider of
nurturing and and being emotionally in
touch and the man is not out providing
strong
but each nurtures each other each can
support each can provide for the other
it's an it that is
an equation of equality and this is
where we're evolving so i don't say when
i'm sharing the male and the female
this is
male and female not man and woman
because a lot of men when when this is
not communicated properly and the female
is rising up now as it has been
predicted that it would and it must
because it's true
but a lot of men feel very alienated
because they say well i'm male what do i
do
what do i do as the females rising up
and they tuck their tail between their
legs and they kind of get emasculated in
this day and age
that's not the point the point is is
that this energy is infinite both male
and female and everybody
and that's it's important to understand
that
but for a long time the male has ruled
over and the left column
uh
traditionally
kabbalah teaches that this is the female
and the male energy and this is the
female but i i differ with that and i
think that it was because the rabbi
identified with the male and knew that
the right column was the source
and so he said well the male must be the
source so he put the right column to be
male and the left column to be female
but it's the opposite the right column
is female
means
intuition facet means compassion
gentleness and netzach is like a
humility
so that those are very feminine energies
to me very female and the left column is
bina it's understanding it's the logical
mind
strength
discernment and hard is a sense of self
confidence itself
when the male dominates then we become
doubled within ourselves
and we're and were at war and that that
is how as it has been that's what leads
to death and disease
oops
let's move a little a quantum level
deeper
we have the mojo cell that is creating
an alchemical union of male and female
where the male is on the outside the
females on the source inside
it creates a balanced positive nature in
its center which is very healing
very healing to be around this my
consciousness has been able to evolve
towards this return
of male and female balance by exposing
myself to the the energy field
of the mojo cell and also drinking the
waters
and when i drink the water i don't drink
like
because there could be a small
quantities of iron and chromium and
nickel that i don't want in my body i
take two three milliliters and i put it
in
a big container of good water live water
and i shake or a swirl or a vortex
and then
because water is such a special
substance which we're learning more and
more about i think there's probably
infinite things that you could do with
water
that small amount of charged water the
consciousness of that water goes into
the rest of the blank water and and
fills it up with that charge
and then you can drink that water and
you have you don't have
toxicity so that's how you do that
and then you have so the mojo cell is
this balanced field
now through time and in the last few
years
an understanding has come to me through
the stars through alchemy through
kabbalah for the most efficient form of
the mojo cell in terms of healing in
terms of aligning our consciousness with
our creator
and here's how it goes here's how it
came to me
in the book of ezekiel ezekiel it says
that it came to pass as i was among the
captives by the river khabar that the
heavens were open and i saw
visions of god
and out of the midst thereof came the
likeness of four living creatures and
this was as for the likeness of their
faces they had the face of a man
and they four had the face of a lion on
the right side and they four had the
face that's the lion
in case you didn't know
you probably know that and the four had
the face of an ox
a bull and they forehead the face of an
eagle
this is ezekiel's vision of god a coded
message perhaps perhaps that's how it
appeared i'm not going to argue with
that i think it may have appeared in
that exact form or it could be a code
doesn't matter
look at john's revelations the exact
same vision described in the same way
and i don't think john was plagiarizing
and i mean that because there are some
movies coming out in particular in the
movie zeitgeist which i differ largely
in part one of its of the way it
expresses itself
part one tries to establish that all of
these similarities that is the
holographic expression of creation
appearing to many different masters and
many different prophets in similar ways
they plagiarized each other
no they saw the same thing
from their different eyes
john
revelations and look behold the door was
opened in heaven
look
the heavens were opened and i saw
visions of god that's ezekiel john says
a door opened in heaven before the
throne there was a sea of glass like
unto crystal and in the midst of the
throne and round about the throne were
four beasts full of eyes
before and behind and the first piece
was like a lion there's the lion again
and the second beast was like a calf the
bull
and the third beast had the face as a
man
and the fourth beast was like a flying
eagle
they say the same exact thing and that
struck me
because
i like astrology
and i said hang on a sec and i wasn't
the first to discover this but i saw it
on the internet that there are people
who have recognized the significance of
this
lion leo
human being is the human child aquarius
eagle is the higher aspect of scorpio
there's scorpio right there the bull
taurus
there are the four fixed signs of the
zodiac which appear as a cross in the
heavens i didn't make the heavens
neither did ezekiel neither did john
they experienced and witnessed something
that is written in the stars which is of
extremely amazing significance
this is the artwork that i did for
what is my galactic heart
centaur
sphinx
we have the eagle we have the eagle nose
we have the bull legs and the bull horns
we have the lion
and we have the human
and the sphinx itself
was said to to have been before its
present form was said to have the the
body of the bull the front paws of the
lion
the face of the man
and at night they would let light
cisterns of fire that gave the
appearance of wings of fire which is
another aspect of scorpio which is this
phoenix that rises from the ashes
scorpio rules
death and transformation and the
resurrection so this the phoenix is the
eagle that has died and been reborn
so this is we're talking a very high
level very powerful level of alchemical
knowledge
which i'm going to explain now
in alchemy this is a book by dennis hawk
it's called the emerald tablet
the artwork shows
soul the king
luna
the moon soul is the sun luna is the
moon the queen and the child
that is created by their union
the goal of the alchemist was not to
make lead into gold that was a sign that
they had what was called the
philosopher's stone which would bring
eternal life
which would eliminate death which would
eliminate darkness in the consciousness
which we have carried for a long time
and
this
this image is very relevant to what i
just shared with you now in the emerald
tablet of thoth
it says that that which is the
philosopher's stone that is the stone of
kings
there is a great pattern which is i'm
paraphrasing now which can be seen
everywhere which is holographic
so yes the alchemists use some
alchemists use the metals to create
their philosopher's stone in in a sealed
vessel
and the crow dying and rising up the the
crow rising up using saturn which was
either antimony or lead most likely
antimony and they went through a process
of alchemy of transformation however the
great pattern states that this this can
appear in other forms
the the symbol if we go back and we look
at
lion the symbol that rules leo
is the sun
the symbol that rules scorpio
in in relation to the sun is the
scorpioism is a water element
and that which rules the water is the
moon
so we have the sun which is known
alchemically as the father and we have
the moon which is known alchemically as
the mother
now the alchemist taught that a planet
the metal that rules the planet the
astrological sign the animals that are
figured are all part of one family that
they are interchangeable so the planet
that rules
uh leo the sun is the same as the sun is
the same as the lion who is the king and
what does the king have on top of the
his head
a crown what is it made of
gold that's the alchemical symbol for
gold and the sun
this is the queen
the mother
which is ruled by the the metal
silver
so we have soul the sun and silver luna
now what happens when you take the sun
fire
and the mother water and you put them
together what do you get
steam somebody said steam
yes thank you ma'am you get a sticker
i have a dragon sticker for you after
the class thank you
so you take fire and you put it in water
you get steam what is steam
vaporize water so you have water in air
what is aquarius known as
the water bearer what element is
aquarius
air
air that carries water is steam
which is caused by the marriage of the
sun and the moon
so
this is explaining that platinum there
are two the the planet that rules
aquarius is uranus oranos and also
saturn before oranos was discovered i
say orano so i don't get those little
those little
chuckles in the crowd when i say uranus
i always laugh too go ahead it's okay i
always laugh
uranus is governed by two metals
alchemically platinum and zinc the
alchemical symbol of platinum is this
showing that the symbol itself which is
which the alchemist gave us
gives us the secret that it is the
element that marries the mother and the
father together it rules the sign
aquarius who is known as the human child
this is the vision of john the vision of
john of revelations the vision of
ezekiel the heavens opening this
knowledge is being revealed to us now so
that we can heal ourselves and return to
our creator
and as i'm showing you now these
elements silver
gold and platinum are magical wonderful
alchemical elements that can be used in
special ways to heal our consciousness
and perhaps even to run our cars i
haven't tried this with our cars but
this may be the optimal form
this is taken from john keeley's secrets
keely knew this
160 years ago because he he created a
wire
which he said made up of sections of
silver gold and platinum respectively is
peculiarly
adapted to transmit concordant
resonant vibrations in their relations
of the thirds their range of molecular
oscillation being in the proportion of
three
six
nine does that sound familiar folks
wow
[Music]
uh oh in case nobody knows what we're
talking about um yesterday dr len
horowitz shared this very sacred
relationship of three six nine get the
lecture it is magnificent
the tr
sorry
master number the trexar is the wire he
called it used as a conductor in
vibratory transmission and for the
multiplication of vibrational
frequencies basically what keeley was
doing was tapping into the zero point
field he discovered that in order to
harness that field to the greatest
degree he created this treksar wire with
silver in the center that is the female
mother in the center
gold on the outside that is the father
male
and platinum that is the neutral balance
which contains
both
the father and the mother
so you have the root note
the harmonic note of the root the
foundation of this this zero point
reality this infinite potential this
healing energy
you have the
the the fifth dominant note which we
could say is we go down
the gold reflects the fifth note from
the do
so
what's created is the third
the third because of the first and the
fifth creates a third the third is the
balance of the root and the dominant
so you have this note
this this harmony this resonant harmony
with the source of god's creation
now let's look at bismuth for a sec
because maybe some of you were saying
well hang on a sec there were four
beasts
four beasts in revelation the human
being aquarius lion leo
eagle scorpio what about the poor bull
we didn't even mention the bull yet look
at this the magnetic susceptibility of
diamagnets such as water is
this symbol
minus
9.05 times 10 to the minus 6. the mostly
strong
the most strongly diametric material is
bismuth
at 1.66 times 10 to the minus 4 which is
around 18 to 20 times that of water
what is the alchemical symbol
for bismuth
forest got it i'll show you the first
one
that's one of them
infinity
where does it go
in our sphere
it goes in the center
what is the other symbol for it
the bull i didn't make this up
the alchemists showed us the signs they
understood creation
they showed us this magical stuff
here is the last beast of the four
beasts of the vision of the creator
the alchemical uh
so taurus is ruled by this planet which
is
venus who is known as the goddess of
love
and beauty
if we bring up the tree of life again
tifaret in the center of the tree of
life the very center is known as beauty
beauty is love love is beauty this is
what
percy shelley said right
percy shelley
no argument
i'm assuming that's correct okay so here
we have
the
the ball
going in the center also because beauty
is in the center of the tree of life
itself and we also know that with this
alchemical symbol
this belongs in the center you remember
my little drawing when you have the male
and the female you create the infinite
which is both the male and the female
coming into each other
so this is my
feeble attempt at creating trexar wire
i took platinum gold silver and spun
them together
and it did work and this is a bismuth
ball it did worth it work it's like an
antenna
for tapping into uh special energies but
it's nothing like kiwis because it's
it's a it's a crude form of it
here is a just a clip i took from the
video that you could go online if you go
to david house productions you can see
more about the sphinx sphere now what
you see here are is copper that is
plated with silver
on the inside platinum in the middle and
gold on the outside
okay
and so we have this this
um when i meditate with this when i pray
with this it's very powerful but it's
not quite as good it would as it would
be if it's the pure metals you
understand
so the the female goes on the inside
this the silver goes on the inside the
platinum is the next shape this is two
inch three inch four inch
david house productions
so i explained that
now this is this teaches us that one the
oneness of the creator is two the father
and the mother male and female that
makes three the father and the mother
unite to create the child which is the
three
now this this also cr is held in the
consciousness of four
one that is two that is three also makes
four what is this the the symbol of
which planet
jupiter what zodiac signed this jupiter
rule
saj sagittarius
sagittarius is a very special
sign that holds all four and if you see
here the sign is really two
that are one
that's also an alchemical sort of hidden
message because sagittarius
is the galact holds the galactic heart
center at 27 degrees which planet earth
is evolving towards
the galactic heart center is coming
towards earth what is the galactic heart
center it's some say it is the heart of
jesus of mary or of yahweh the i am
presence the mayans saw it as the great
maw where all souls came from and where
all souls were turned to upon death
in the stars there's a myth that refers
to a serpent of light
that
resides in the heavens and that's the
the milky way and where the serpent eats
its own tail
is the point of of 27 degrees
sagittarius which is a black hole
at the center of the galaxy
where a tremendous amount of energy is
is released where matter and antimatter
are merging coming from the black hole
and from the universe itself
so we are aligning galactically 2012 is
in alignment with this energy which
represents the heart of christ the heart
of the creator the heart
of the balance of the male and female
which is the aruba rules
this is where we're evolving to whether
we like it or not whether we sit on our
porch and say damn it i'm a man and i'm
not getting down with the female
or we say the opposite being a woman we
are evolving towards this point and and
so it behooves us
to
understand how to let go of the control
of the opposite extremes and find the
union of opposites
uh okay i explained that black hole this
is the mojo we're back to the mojo
hallelujah thank you
when you sit in a car
and you put your mojo cell connected to
your negative battery then the negative
goes to the center
the negative of the center plate the
center sphere carries the energy of the
center and it attaches to the car itself
and once it does that it creates an
energy field on the entire chassis
the entire metallic frame of the car is
grounded to the negative of the battery
you're sitting in a healing space
you're sitting in a balanced space
and you feel it
oops
does that mean that um time's up
uh just some brief charging methods
using hot electricity that is
destructive electricity that is
electricity when you go like this
you can die
is not ideal
the mojo evolution is going to be using
uh stuff like the bedini schoolgirl
project which is creating radiant energy
actually i'm going to skip this video
but you can get it online at my uh
can we skip that john
oops uh okay good no problem i got it
what we're going to be looking at also
is charging with stuff like tesla
technology
which uses a very basic principle of you
have your source voltage you have a
spark gap your capacitor this is taken
from peter lindemann's uh it's actually
a tesla patent but that's where i took
it from peter linneman's the free energy
secrets of cold electricity
your your
pulse dc this is dc
induce causes a current to flow in this
primary wire which induces a magnetic
field in the secondary wire a secondary
coil
when the pulse goes out
the magnetic field that was induced in
the secondary collapses
and the universe flows in with energy
it's inviting instead of pushing against
we're inviting the energy to fill up a
space that is now empty
and when it becomes filled it becomes
filled with a lot more than what we put
in
this is coming from the void from the
zero point field so we're looking at
solutions now to charge the cells with
this now when i say cells i mean the
mojo cell and the sphinx sphere
and if we move forward this is just
another thing
we're going to put the cell there
or or there as the capacitor
or both
if we use the frequencies that
dr len horowitz shared with us yesterday
as pulse dc
with the sphinx sphere
i believe that we were are making the
elixir of life
literally the vibrational essence of
that which heals the tree of life
reality
we are so blessed in this day and age to
have access to this
the alchemists for thousands of years
have kept secrets hidden
what i feel i'm revealing to you is one
of the great patterns of the emerald
tablets of thoth a holographic fractal
that reveals the nature the alchemical
nature of the balanced positive nature
of the creator using silver gold and
platinum
so we want to apply
high voltage high frequency and very low
current
it's pulse dc
a split frequency general generator
apply the root note
frequency to the inner sphere tuned to
528 hertz the vibration of love
and just wait and see what happens i'm
just thinking about it now and i'm
vibrating i can't wait to go home and
apply it
now this requires some funding
so if you are sitting on a mattress
filled with cash
and you would like to help support this
project with the sphinx sphere i would
really appreciate it
i'm revealing this knowledge freely go
out and build it yourself it's not that
expensive a few thousand dollars
manufacture the spheres get in touch
with me you want to know exactly how to
do it
make these things everywhere
make this vibration available to people
bring them over let them drink the water
created from this let them pray and
meditate from this just using the copper
spheres that are plated with just a
little bit of these substances like
you're talking about just a few
molecules thick
was incredible
imagine when it's pure i haven't even
gotten there yet this is this is to
happen so i could really use their
support if you're interested
really really
now and one other thing if we can find
an intersection of schumann's frequency
let's say it is increasing let's say
it's 12 hertz now
so 12 hertz any resonant harmony any um
octave of that 24 48 96 etcetera
etcetera that we can find that
intersects with a free a harmonic of
that then we have the earth
resonant frequency resonating with this
magical number in a cell that is created
to balance the male and the female
wow so stay in touch this is free now
this is free to be used to be used in
healing
and to be used like i said possibly for
our cars and our motorcycles and our
airplanes let's see where it goes let's
see where it goes i'm almost done john
i'm almost done
this is mojo working where you can find
more information and like i said we need
sponsors also for this i want to go to
produce a lot of cells so that people
everywhere will be having these uh cells
that are created in the same shape
they'll start to resonate together
and the more that are out there the more
the mojo will have a potential to tap in
and i'm also um going to be
uh i'm also going to be um offering
distributorships if you're interested in
disseminating this stuff part of it and
we have one car cell left which is
polished
so it'll cost a little extra but it's
available now and i would love if you're
interested in getting this to have it in
your home for the healing aspect of it
please come and back order it like order
it now uh it would help me a lot to go
into production it will help a lot
this is my other work the book that we
were talking about at thelast4books.com
a book on on naturopathic medicine and
this is david house productions which is
sort of the umbrella website that that
houses the the work that i'm doing
now the last thing i want to share with
you is very important i won't go too
much into it i would love to spend
an hour on it
but it's this plan called every
nationland.com also newtopia.cc
this is the vision that john lennon had
of a world united
it's a simple nature of the world where
all people all races all religions come
together as one
we're going to be having forums
forums about the sphinx sphere forums
about the mojo cell you go you sign up
you become an utopian
you become a part of every nation land
and you will have access to the most
cutting edge advanced knowledge that is
coming to us
of how to heal the world how to heal
ourselves
i thank you all so much for for
being um
here to share this with me
i think i'll stop there thank you thank
you
ladies and gentlemen moshe daniel thank
you thank you um
we are running a little bit tight in
time i uh
if we have one or two quick questions uh
no more than that but if you guys can
obey if if i can beg your grace if you
can see him out front at his table if
it's something you can answer at the
table uh is it something you could
answer get answered at the table there
okay
um
then uh thank you very much the question
doesn't answer the table
okay um let's uh let's take five minutes
and then